迈克:爸爸,我们本不想打扰你,而且明天还要上学呢.我知道我们该睡觉了.不过你介意我和本看晚间电影么?不好拒绝吧!谢谢爸爸,你真理解我们.
Mike: Ah, Dad, we don't want to disturb you.I've known the school night.We
know we should be in bed.But would you mind that Ben and I sit
up to watch the late movie on cable tonight?It's hard to abolish too.Thank
you, dad, you are very understanding
麦琪:嘿!小家伙们.
Maggie: Hi, guys.
迈克和本:妈妈.
Mike and Ben: Mom.
麦琪:哦,已经很晚了,快去睡觉吧!
Maggie: Oh, now you are going to bed because it's so late.
本:好吧!
Ben: Not.
麦琪:亲爱的,你真好!又在等我回来.
Maggie: Oh, honey, that's so sweet of you to wait up for me again.
杰森:以为我们还有很多话要谈,
Jason:'Cause we will have a lot to talk about.
这是我俩仅有的单独时间.
This is the only time we have.
麦琪:亲爱的,真是抱歉!
Maggie: Oh, honey, I am sorry, work was so late again.
我又回来晚了,最近编辑部的专题节目又有新的问题.
But this feature series turn into more work than I imagine.
杰森:什么专题节目?
Jason: What feature series?
麦琪:杰森,难道你就真的不知道我在说什么呀?
Maggie: Jason, you don't have a clue what I am talking about?
杰森:当然知道,上周你就跟我讲过了.
Jason: Of course I did.You told me all about it last week.
麦琪:不是,是昨晚.
Maggie: Last night.
杰森:啊!对的,是昨晚.
Jason: Ah, indeed.Last night.
麦琪:不不!等等,你当时根本就没听.
Maggie: No, no.wait a minute, you couldn't possibly listen.
杰森:我听了,我以迈克的名义发誓.
Jason: I did, I swear in Mike's life.
麦琪:不!我记得我想告诉你之前就睡着了.
Maggie: No, I just remembered that I fell asleep before I told you.
迈克:谁把这个消息透露给迈克的.
Mike: Hum hum, as going to break the news to Mike.
麦琪:真是对不起!这几天我真是忙晕了.
Maggie: I am so sorry; I am so befuddled these days.
杰森:好了,
Jason: It's ok.It's ok.
好了.不过你得记住一件事,
The important thing to remember here, sweetheart,
那就是并不是完全是我的错.
is I wasn't in the wrong at all.
麦琪:你生气了?
Maggie: You are mad at me.
杰森:怎么会哪?我为何要生你的气?什么烧饭,
Jason: No, come on, why was I mad at you?
打扫卫生,洗衣服之类的家务,我都不介意做!
I don't mind doing all the cooking and cleaning and laundering.
麦琪:杰森,我不知道这些家务还怎么这么费时间!
Maggie: Oh, Jason, I didn't know this job would be so demanding.
杰森:我有提洗衣服吗?
Jason: Did I mention the laundering?
麦琪:是的,而且说了两遍.
Maggie: twice.
杰森:好了,我现在必须趁机告诉你我们的房顶得整理修一下.
Jason: Yeah, I must take the chance to tell you.Getting the roof fixed.
麦琪:我爱你.
Maggie: I love you.
杰森:别岔开话题.
Jason: Hum, not distract me.
麦琪:我没有.
Maggie: I won't.
杰森:我们现在有许多的选择方案.
Jason: We have a plenty of options to discuss.
麦琪:哦,听起来不赖.
Maggie: Oh, it sounds interesting.
杰森:是的,到时再叫个工匠,这样就不会花很多钱.
Jason: Well, yes.There is a handy man, who is, by the way, is far
cheaper, and
麦琪:哦,已经十一点了.
Maggie: Oh, It's 11.
杰森:快去睡吧
Jason: Let's go to bed.
杰森:我想我们还有东西没谈.
Jason: I think we were about to have a conversation.
麦琪:静静!下面是我的专题报道片.
Maggie: Hush...the feature series is next.
杰森:嘘……
Jason: Hush...
麦琪:嘿!
Maggie: Hi, I am Maggie Malone all this week,
我是麦琪·马龙,
all this spotlighting physicals on wheels.
这周我要介绍的是流动医院,流动医院的目的是进行健康检查的,
Mobile vans provide a checkup curbside.
今天我的节目合作伙伴是博嗨医生.
With me today is project coordinator Doctor Buhl.
医生:是的.
Doctor: Yup.
麦琪:医生,你觉得是不是每个人都应该进行身体的健康检查?
Maggie: Doctor, don't you think we should have it even we feel being healthy?
医生:是的.
Doctor: Yup.
麦琪:我们在这一周将会看到流动医院整个的工作流程,
Maggie: And all this week,
因为我自己在这部有趣的系列专题的拍摄过程中,
you will see how the physicals on wheels works as this report undergoes
将会经历了一次全面的体格检查.
a complete compelling and riveting series.
杰森:麦琪,快醒醒!
Jason: Well, Maggie, wake up.
麦琪:对不起,我们说到哪里了?
Maggie: Oh, I am sorry.What will we say?
杰森:你都睡着了,怎么可能知道我在说什么呢?
Jason: What have you assumed if you fell asleep when I was talking?
麦琪:抱歉!
Maggie: I am sorry.
杰森:行了,我记得最后我们是在看你的专题新闻.
Jason: Well, the last thing I remember, we were watching your news feature.
麦琪:是的!哦不!刚才放专题新闻的时候我们居然都睡着了.
Maggie: That's right.Oh, no.we fell asleep during my news cast.
杰森:亲爱的,那只是凑巧.
Jason: Honey, it happens.
麦琪:是不是很枯燥,对吧?
Maggie: It was boring, wasn't it?
杰森:我不知道是不是枯燥,以为我刚刚也睡着了.
Jason: I don't know if it was boring, I fell asleep.
麦琪:把灯关掉.
Maggie: Turn out the light?
杰森:麦琪,是天亮了,你叫我怎么关呀?
Jason: Only God can turn out the light, Maggie, it's morning.
麦琪:杰森,杰森,我要迟到了,我可不能迟到呀!
Maggie: Jason, Jason, I am late.I cannot be late.
杰森:亲爱的,不用急.
Jason: Honey, relaxed.Come on.You worked late last night.
昨晚你工作的太晚了,一个星期以来你一直这样.
You worked late all last week.
麦琪:亲爱的,你怎么还不明白?
Maggie: Honey, You just don't get it, do you?
我现在还是个新手,我得努力提高自己,
I am still new one on this job.I've got to improve myself constantly.
这样的压力可不小,你要知道电视节目是个男人占主导的世界.
That's not easy either.TV news is a man's world.
杰森:那样的话,你就不要穿的那么招摇了!
Jason: Well, in that case, you want to hit your boss with my boxy shirt?
本:我的早餐哪?爸爸妈妈都去哪里了?
Ben: I want my breakfast, Where the hacker mom and dad?
迈克:我们不再是小孩了,做个早餐也不是很难.
Mike: We are not kids anymore.I mean, how hard could it be to make breakfast?
好了,本,
Ha ha, all right, Ben, you've got the pizza from last night.
吃些昨晚剩下的披萨吧!你想要没馅的还是加凤尾鱼的.
What do you want, plain or Anchovy?
本:加凤尾鱼.
Ben: Anchovy.
开萝尔:冷披萨当早饭,谁还吃的下.
Carol: Cold pizza for breakfast I see is disgusting.
迈克:对呀!我们最好加加热.
Mike: Yeah, you are right, we'd better heat it.
麦琪:我刚说我在和一群努力工作的男人竞争,
Maggie: I'm just saying I am competing with men who don't mind working
但是他们的妻子却因为他们长期不管家务而吵着离婚.
long hours because his wife divorced him years ago for working long out.
杰森:你这话是什么意思?
Jason: But that explains everything.
开萝尔:妈妈爸爸,今天我不用做早饭了.
Carol: Mom and Dad, I had nothing to do with getting breakfast this morning.
麦琪:好了,你还是过来帮我一下吧,开萝尔!
Maggie: Well, you could pitch in your help, Carol.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
本:迈克,那是我的馅饼!
Ben: That was my pie, Mike.
杰森:你们拿披萨当早餐?
Jason: Pizza for breakfast?
迈克:是的,开萝尔不肯教我和本煮鸡蛋.
Mike: Yeah, well, Carol wouldn't show little Ben and me how to make eggs.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
杰森:我教你们如何做一份可口的早餐.
Jason: I'll show you.A good breakfast are today, right?
杰森:鸡蛋在哪?麦琪.
Jason: Eggs, Maggie?
麦琪:早晨就吃鸡蛋真是倒胃口.
Maggie: Just a thought of eggs makes me sick.
本:披萨怎么样?是加凤尾鱼的那种.
Ben: How about pizza?It's Anchovy.
麦琪:那还行!
Maggie: That does sound good.
杰森:亲爱的怎么了?
Jason: Honey?
麦琪:还有没有胡椒纷和奶酪?
Maggie: Is there some peppers and cheese?
麦克:本,做的不错,你让妈妈突然开胃了.
Mike: Now, you've done Ben, you give mom right over the age.
麦琪:那就拿一个吧!
Maggie: Got one.
杰森:麦琪?亲爱的怎么了?
Jason: Maggie?Honey?
麦琪:怎么了?
Maggie: Yeah?
杰森:我有个注意,既然我们在家没时间谈谈,
Jason: I have an idea.
那中午吃饭时一起谈谈怎样?
Since we cannot find a time to talk at home, when will we have lunch today?
麦琪:我不知道中午到时有没有胃口.
Maggie: I don't know, I haven't had that much appetite really.
杰森:我想利用午餐时间我们可以谈谈,
Jason: Well, a lunch will give us a chance to catch up on things,
家里不光只是屋顶漏雨的事情.
just a lot going on around here, such as leaky roof.
麦琪:房顶漏雨!你怎么没跟我讲?
Maggie: The roof leaks, why didn't you tell me?
杰森:昨晚我跟你讲过!
Jason: I did, last night.
麦琪:是的,你讲过房顶漏雨.
Maggie: Yeah, that roof leaked.
杰森:我想我们必须一起吃个午饭.
Jason: We definitely should have lunch.
麦琪:好的,那得看我又没时间,一点怎样?
Maggie: Sure, I can pencil you and at....One?
杰森:怎么还要预约?
Jason: Pencil me?I have to have an appointment?
麦琪:杰森,别蠢了!
Maggie: Jason, don't be silly.This is not an appointment.
这可不是什么约会,要不推倒明天上午九点怎样?
Or we have lunch tomorrow at 9.
杰森:就今天下午一点了!
Jason: Hey.....Today at one is fine.
本:爸爸,你想来块馅饼还是什么也不吃了?
Ben: Hi, dad, you want just a slice of pizza or you escape breakfast?
麦琪:德尔玛,西德尔威蒂先生去哪里了?
Maggie: Delmar, I've been waiting for Mr.Sid Sidlevich all morning.
我都等他一上午了.
Where is he?
德尔玛:去打网球了.若没有什么重要的事的话,那他就在和市长谈话.
Delmar: Racket ball.If anyone unimportant asks, He is meeting with the mayor.
麦琪:我必须要和他谈谈,五分钟就好了.
Maggie: Well I only need 5 minutes this time.I have to talk to him.
德尔玛:什么事?
Delmar: What about?
麦琪:不知昨晚你有没有看我制作的健康系列专题片?
Maggie: Did you happen to see part one of my health series last night?
德尔玛:抱歉,那时我已经睡了.
Delmar: I am sorry, I fell asleep.
麦琪:即使长岛人都把它当成催眠曲,我也不奇怪,
Maggie: I wouldn't be surprised if I put all of long islands sleep.
那是我一星期的健康检查,有人看才怪!
That was one I take a physical all week?
一男人:这里有没有签约纸?
A Man: Is there any sign sheet on this?
麦琪:没有.
Maggie: No.
德尔玛:麦琪,西德尔威蒂先生随时可能回来,
Delmar: Maggie, Mr.Sid Sidlevich will be back any minute.
要是他打赢了,他会显得非常友善的.
If he won, he will be in terrific mood.
麦琪:哦,西德尔威蒂先生,能不能和你交谈几分钟?
Maggie: Oh, Mr.Sid Sidlevich, could I talk to you for just several minutes?
西德尔威蒂先生:克劳斯博士,把你的德国烟拿到我的办公室来,大预言家先生
Sid Sidlevich: Doctor Clite, get your crug bug my office now, Mr.Weather Mister.
德尔玛:先生,下次你肯定会赢的.
Delmar: You'll win next time, sir.
麦琪:现在我哪里也不去,我一定要在午饭和他谈谈.
Maggie: I am not going anywhere.I've got to talk to him before lunch.
西德尔威蒂先生:太差劲了,一点也没有军人那种雄赳赳,气昂昂的气势,你到底都是在想什么?
Sid Sidlevich: A long pressure, friend, does not roll across the mat like an army
on the march, well, how were you thinking
麦琪:还是等到午饭后吧!
Maggie: After lunch is good.
西德尔威蒂先生:你们有那种气势吗?
Sid Sidlevich: Do you have that?
克劳斯博士:……
Doctor Clite :...
麦琪:西德尔威蒂先生,我想和你谈谈.
Maggie: Mr.Sidlevich, I've just to talk with you.
西德尔威蒂先生:你在等会,
Sid Sidlevich: Maggie, this is going to have to wait,
我要去一下洗手间.
I've got to go somewhere.
麦琪:那我和你一起去.
Maggie: I'll go with you.
西德尔威蒂先生:随便.
Sid Sidlevich: Fine.
麦琪:我等不了啦!
Maggie: I can wait.
德尔玛:博嗨医生.
Delmar: Doctor Buhl.
麦琪:好的,医生,今天下午三点,好的,健康检查全套程序.我会带来的,装在瓶子里,好的,再见.
Maggie: Yes, hi, doctor.Yes, it's afternoon at 3.Yes, the whole physical complete workout.Yes, I'll bring it.In a bottle.Right, bye.
体育记者:掌握球权就是致胜的法宝.
Sport Reporter: A ball control is everything.
西德尔威蒂先生:你说你是体育记者弗兰克,
Sid Sidlevich: Look, you call yourself as sports reporter Frank,
可杰博士是篮球世上最优秀运动员.
Doctor Jay was the best basketball player in the history of the game.
麦琪:我应该把他堵在厕所里.
Maggie: I should've stayed in there when I had of the corner in your honor.
德尔玛:麦琪,他们叫你去编片子.
Delmar: Maggie, they need you in editing.
麦琪:哦……
Maggie: Oh...
门卫:马龙太太,我想知道这个人是谁?
Guard: Mrs.Malone.Any possible idea of this squirrel?
麦琪:这家伙是我的丈夫.
Maggie: This squirrel is my husband.
拉尔夫:但为什么他的驾照上写着西沃
Ruffer: But why just the driver license says his name is Seaver?
麦琪:我的姓是西沃.
Jason: My name is Seaver.
麦琪:把他放了,拉尔夫
Maggie: Please release him, Ruffer.
拉尔夫:好的,马龙太太.
Ruffer: It was a pleasure, Mr.Marlon.
麦琪:杰森,我们的午餐时间还差五分钟.
Maggie: Jason, our lunch wasn't until one o'clock, it's only 5 to.
杰森:那人还对搜了身.
Jason: That man frisked me.
麦琪:哦,每一个人他都搜.
Maggie: Oh, Rougher frisks everybody.
杰森:那就算了.
Jason: That'll be ok.
麦琪:我还要去编个一分钟的短片,完了我们就走,
Maggie: I have to run the edit just one minute.
我马上回来.
Then we can go, I'll be right back, accounts.
杰森:他说要查武器,可是谁会带那东西?
Jason: He checked for weapons in places they couldn't possibly be.
麦琪:你真是善解人意!
Maggie: You are so understanding.
杰森:这还说得过去.
Jason: Wasn't that bad.
弗兰克:你又没看到Wilt还在打?
Frank: Did you ever see Wilt still playing?
西德尔威蒂先生:当然看到了,不过我看他的防守不太好.
Sid Sidlevich: Of course I did.But the man couldn't play defense well.Did he?
弗兰克:但是他来回推挡了432次
Frank: But he did have blocked 432 shots.
西德尔威蒂先生:你怎么知道他推挡了432次?
Sid Sidlevich : How do you know he blocked 432 shots?
弗兰克:我数的.
Frank: I counted them, ok?
杰森:我也喜欢杰博士.
Jason: I like Doctor Jay myself.
西德尔威蒂先生:快看那边!
Sid Sidlevich: There, see?
西德尔威蒂先生:你被聘用了,以前做过体育评论员吗?
Sid Sidlevich: You are hired, ever do sports casting before?
弗兰克:哈哈,你真是风趣,中午吃饭时再见.
Frank: Ha ha, You're funny.I'll see you at lunch.
西德尔威蒂先生:我就喜欢让他难堪,
Sid Sidlevich: Ha...I'd like to do him a hard time.
你以前做过体育评论员吗?
Are you with sports cast by the way?
杰森:没有,我是一个心理医生.我叫杰森·西沃,玛姬·马龙的丈夫.
Jason: No, no, I am a psychiatrist.I am Jason Seaver.Maggie Marlon's husband.
西德尔威蒂先生:是吗,认识你很高兴!
Sid Sidlevich: Oh, yeah, it's especially fine to meet you.Sid Sidlevich.
我叫西德尔威蒂.那么你也是杰博士的球迷吗?
So you're big doctor Jay's fan?
杰森:我才没开玩笑,
Jason: Oh, yeah, kidding?
我当医生就是受了他的影响.
Doctor Jay is the reason why I became a doctor myself.
西德尔威蒂先生:有机会我会告诉他的.
Sid Sidlevich: Oh, I got you kid that I'll tell him then.
杰森:你认识杰博士?
Jason: You know doctor Jay?
西德尔威蒂先生:弗兰克中餐的时候会采访他,我也会参加,
Sid Sidlevich: Frank is interviewing him at lunch, I am horning in,
你要不要一起去?
care to come along?
杰森:要是真的能见到杰博士,截取左右臂我也愿意,
Jason: To meet the doctor, in person?Are you kidding?You can get my left arm.
不过不和我妻子去吃午餐她会发火的.
My right arm. Oh, my wife... Not good to take her to lunch.
西德尔威蒂先生:要是你想去,我来帮你应付她.
Sid Sidlevich: Well, I can keep her busy if you duck out.
麦琪:打扰了.
Maggie: Excuse me.
西德尔威蒂先生:麦琪,我知道你在那.
Sid Sidlevich: Maggie, I know you were over there.
杰森:我也一样
Jason: Me too.
麦琪:中午我丈夫想和我一起吃个饭.
Maggie: Well, my husband and I will have lunch today.
西德尔威蒂先生:但他准备跟我们走.
Sid Sidlevich: But he is coming with us.
麦琪:这样吗?
Maggie: Yes?
杰森:是的.
Jason: Oh, yeah.
西德尔威蒂先生:麦琪,你不一起去吗?
Sid Sidlevich: Maggie, do you want to tag along?
麦琪:我可不想绞你们的局.
Maggie: I sure don't want to be in the way.
西德尔威蒂先生:没关系的,来吧!
Sid Sidlevich: Don't worry about it.Come on.
麦琪:杰森,这是不是你的主意?
Maggie: Jason, is it your idea?
杰森:不,这是他的,哈哈,太好了.
Jason: no, It's his....hahaha......great
杰森:看看他在这上面写了什么!从朱里亚到杰森,从杰博士到另一个博士
Jason: Look at the lines on this, from Julia to Jason, one Doctor Jay and I.
弗兰克:跟你讲什么?你最好还是想想怎么应付你的老婆吧!
Frank: Tell you what?You'd better tell that baby frank or start this smell.
杰森:西德,我怎么感谢你?
Jason: Sid, how can I thank you?
西德尔威蒂先生:不用这么客气,很高兴认识你,下次再见.
Sid Sidlevich: You can't.Nice to meet you, Jason see you again.
杰森:麦琪,你怎么没告诉过我西德是个球迷?麦琪,你现在在哪里?
Jason: Maggie, you didn't tell me Sid was a sports nut.Maggie?Where are you in?
麦琪:我没赶上去吃饭的电梯,就一直在这儿等.
Maggie: I missed the elevator to lunch, I have been here the whole time.
杰森:不会吧,走吧!你怎么了?不,
Jason: Oh, no, you were not, come on, were you?
我看到你也进去了,就一声不响地坐在最后那张桌子,一声也不吭.
No, I saw you going there, at the end of the table sitting there all quiet.
麦琪:很好.
Maggie: Very good.
杰森:好吧,待回见,我去配个眼镜.杰博士是个令人难以置信的运动员.宝贝,这是我们最美好的一顿午餐.
Jason: Well, see you at home.I'll get this a frame.Oh.....Unbelievable, Doctor Jay
Yes.......Honey, thanks for the best lunch we have ever had together.Yeah
德尔玛:我来回答你的问题.不,他没意识到他那猪一样的模样.
Delmar: I answered you the questions.No, he doesn't realize that he is totally a piggy fan.
西德尔威蒂先生:麦琪,我想和你谈谈.
Sid Sidlevich: Maggie, I need to talk to you.
麦琪:哦,机会来了.
Maggie: Oh, coming.Finally been what the guys at lunch paid off.Yes, Sid.
一起吃午餐终于有效果了.西德尔威蒂先生我想谈谈我的健康系列专题了.
I want to talk to you about my health series.
西德尔威蒂先生:我现在没时间和你谈这件事,
Sid Sidlevich: I don't have any time to talk about that.
我想问你今晚你们家里有什么安排吗?
Do you family plan for tonight?
麦琪:什么?哦,家里没安排,我可以晚些回去的,我们可以晚些时候再谈谈.
Maggie: What?Oh, well, no.I can stay late.We can talk about this later.
西德尔威蒂先生:我可不行!我有今晚的球赛票,可以带家属去.
Sid Sidlevich: Nor can I do.Here is the ticket for the NEX game for
tonight family come through
麦琪:球赛?
Maggie: the NEX?
西德尔威蒂先生:是的,球赛太令人兴奋了,我只是希望你让杰森和我一起去看.
Sid Sidlevich: Yeah, I am pretty darn excited by it myself.I just want to
make sure if Jason would be free to join me
麦琪:好的,晚上他是最闲的.
Maggie: He is free, all right.
开萝尔:本,看看我是怎么调制这么美味的调料的.
Carol: Perfect, Ben.What you learn is I carefully whisk the delicate white sauce.
本:现在要是有一罐花生酱和一支调羹我就满足了,
Ben: All some series I could be very happy with a jam of peanut butter
即便没有调羹也可以.
on the spoon.I don't even need spoon.
迈克:嘿!开萝尔,你那精美的白色调汁怎么变棕色了?
Mike: Hi, Carol, how comes it your delicate white sauce is brown.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
本:火!
Ben: Fire!
开萝尔:哦,不,我的红头鱼.
Carol: Oh, no, my snapper scraggy.
开萝尔:显然烧好后会小一点的.
Carol: It's supposed to shrink a little when you cook it.
本:干脆再烧一会.
Ben: Cook it some more, a lot more.
开萝尔:本,这可是很有营养的.
Carol: Ben, it's very nutritious.
迈克:本,你知道只要爸爸去看篮球赛,我们肯定要吃一些没有营养价值的东西.
Mike: You know, Ben, if dad leaves for basketball games, we get some with no
nutritional value whatsoever
玛姬:嘿!孩子们.
Maggie: Hi, everybody.
迈克:妈妈,你在这干什么?
Mike: Mom, What are you doing here?
麦琪:我家在这里啊!
Maggie: I live here.
本:太好了,开饭了.
Ben: It's great, there goes dinner.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: Pardon me?
开萝尔:因为你们没回来,所以他们就只好吃我做的东西了.
Carol: They are just mad, since you are here.They have to eat the fired
meal I cooked
麦琪:你们爸爸没做晚饭就去看球了?
Maggie: Didn't you get your good father making you dinner before his big game?
开萝尔:是我自愿要做晚饭的.
Carol: I volunteered to cook.
麦琪:好啊,杰森,看来好像他连垃圾也没有倒掉.
Maggie: Nice Jason, Nice.It smells like he didn't take out the garbage either.
本:那不是垃圾的味道,那是开萝尔烧的红头鱼的味道.
Ben: That's not the garbage.That is Carol's snapper.
杰森:你怎么了?
Jason: What do you think?
麦琪:你可是个成年人,还象个小孩一样准备了围兜,叫我怎么说你呢?
Maggie: So you are grown up, really did frame a lobster bit.
杰森:我想我最好把它挂起来,但是挂哪里呢?
Jason: I think It should go all right over the...
麦琪:车里面吧!
Maggie: Volvo.
杰森:车现在在车库里.
Jason: Volvo is in the garage.
麦琪:太棒了!
Maggie: That's right.
杰森:好了,你怎么了?
Jason: Well, come on, What is it?
麦琪:哦,没有呀!你还是享受你的篮球赛吧!
Maggie: Oh, Nothing.You are enjoying your basketball game?
杰森:麦琪,我知道你是怎么回事了!今天是你第一次早回家,你想知道为什么我要出去吗?
Jason: I know what it is, Maggie.You think, Hey, it's first night you are
early at home, and why I am going out
麦琪:想啊!为什么?
Maggie: Yes, why?
杰森:亲爱的,晚上出去我不想找任何借口.
Jason: Honey, it's not for a silly reason.
麦琪:是为了你的篮球吧!去吧!我会理解的.
Maggie: I know, it's basketball, I understand.
杰森:好吧,谢谢.
Jason: Well, thank you for your......
但要是你不想让我去,我也没关系,
But if you don't want me to go out,
你我都是成年人,
I recognize my responsibility in this relationship as an adult.
要是你不让我去,你就直说好了.
If you don't want me to go, just say don't go.
麦琪:别去了.
Maggie: Don't go.
杰森:哦,亲爱的,行行好吧!这票很贵的,不去看太可惜了.
Jason: Oh, the nit.Honey, come on, the court side seats, they are expensive seats.
麦琪:我就知道你想去.
Maggie: I knew you wanted to go.
杰森:刚刚你还说你能理解我的.
Jason: Well, you just said you understand.
麦琪:你刚刚不是也说你不去吗?
Maggie: You just said you wouldn't go.
杰森:我不是那意思.
Jason: I didn't mean it.
麦琪:那好,我也不是那意思
Maggie: Well, Nor did I.
杰森:那一定是西德
Jason: That must be Sid.
麦琪:让你的好朋友西德等久了可不好.
Maggie: We don't want to keep your good buddy Sid waiting.
西德尔威蒂先生:麦琪!
Sid Sidvich: Maggie
麦琪:嘿!西德尔威蒂先生!
Maggie: Hi, Mr.Sidvich.
西德尔威蒂先生:杰森!
Sid Sidvich: Jason.
杰森:嘿!西德!
Jason: Hi, Sid.
西德尔威蒂先生:嘿!你都准备好了吗?
Sid Sidvich: Hey, You are ready for a great game?
麦琪:你俩要是不想错过开球时间,那就最好快点.
Maggie: Well, you guys had better hurry up if don't want to miss the kickoff.
西德尔威蒂先生:不,开球是足球里的术语,在篮球里这叫……
Sid Sidvich: No, that's football.And in basketball, it's called...
麦琪:跳球,我知道!开个玩笑!
Maggie: The tip-up.I know.It was a joke.
麦琪:谢谢你了,杰森!
Maggie: Thanks off bunch, Jason.
你怎么还在这里,我以为你去看球去了?
What are you doing, you were going to the game?
杰森:你这么不高兴!
Jason: Well, I am not about to go off to a silly basketball game when
那我又怎么能去看这场无聊的球赛哪?
you are so upset.
麦琪:你是说你为了我就不和我老板去吃饭了!
Maggie: You mean you cancelled on my boss just for me?
杰森:我不去看了.
Jason: Give up the Nex.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,那真是太好了.
Maggie: Oh, honey, that's so nice.
杰森:对我来说,即便是球场最好的位置也不如你重要.
Jason: Well, even the court side seat is not as important as you.
麦琪:我会把这张球票裱起来.
Maggie: I may frame this ticket...
杰森:好的.
Jason: Yeah.
麦琪:干脆把它……
Maggie: Better yet I mean.
杰森:不,不,不!
Jason: No, no, no!
麦琪:我想安静一会,你还是去球场吧.
Maggie: So as soon as you pass by me, that is after the game.
杰森:不知还会不会有加时赛?
Jason: It's expected for a long fight?
麦琪:去吧!杰逊,你还是去吧!
Maggie: Go, Jason, go.
杰森:哦,是你让我去的.
Jason: Oh you say you want me to go.
麦琪:是
Maggie: Yeah.
杰森:好吧.
Jason: Ok.
杰森:我还是呆在家里了.
Jason: I am staying.
麦琪:好,我该去睡了.
Maggie: Good, I am going to bed.
杰森:不,麦琪,
Jason: No.Why don't we talk, Maggie?
为什么我们不好好谈谈?我们不如就从房顶维修开始吧?
Why don't we start with the roof repair situation?
麦琪:不谈也许会更好些!
Maggie: Maybe it's better if we don't.
杰森:你怎么这么酸刻呀?
Jason: Why are you so edgy?
麦琪:杰森,我想谈谈其他事,
Maggie: Jason, I was hoping for a conversation about something other than
而不是这些琐事.
little things.
杰森:麦琪,房顶维修也是大事呀!
Jason: Maggie, the leaking roof is not little thing.
麦琪:你就不能自己想想办法去修?
Maggie: Can you fix it yourself?
杰森:我当然可以,我们不是一直都在讨论一些琐事吗?
Jason: Well, of course I could.We always discuss the little things.
麦琪:那你承认房顶维修也是琐事了.
Maggie: So you admit the roof is a little thing.
杰森:我为什么不和西德去看球赛?
Jason: Why didn't I just go to the game with Sid.
麦琪:杰森,我可不想谈我的老板,还是说说房顶维修的事情吧!
Maggie: Jason I would rather talk about the roof than my boss.
杰逊:一定得谈谈你的老板.
Jason: That's definitely about your boss.
麦琪:我不谈他一个,要谈就谈你和他.
Maggie: Oh, it is?It is about you and my boss.
你俩很默契,而且玩得很高兴,
You two are powers, hitting it off, having the final time.
而我却在为引起一个男人的重视拼命努力,但我还是失败了.
While I am trying my damned skit to get attention of a man, I barely see.
杰森:亲爱的,现在我不是在这吗?
Jason: Honey, I am here.
麦琪:不是你,
Maggie: Not you, my boss.
是我的老板.
You meet the guy just 2 minutes and you are invited to lunch.
你和他认识才两分钟就一起去午餐,可我等了一个上午连见他五分钟都不行,
I can't get 5 minutes of his time after waiting all morning.
甚至还跟着他进了男厕所.
I even went to men's room with him.
杰森:那好吧,下次见到他我不会再那么友好了.
Jason: All right, so, next time I meet your boss.I will not be so friendly.
麦琪:杰森,你怎么就不理解我呢?
Maggie: Jason, can you understand me?
你老实讲,你们之间只有纯粹的友谊吗?
And honestly tell me you are just being friendly?
杰森:是的,要不然你就得去女厕所了!
Jason: Yes, you went to the men's room with Sid?
麦琪:别想转移话题.
Maggie: Don't change the subject.
杰森:什么话题?
Jason: What's the subject ?
麦琪:你的真正动机.
Maggie: You are hiding motives.
杰森:可是我什么也没做呀!
Jason: I have none.
麦琪:难道在潜意识中也没有想过.比如说,
Maggie: Not even on the subconscious level?
你想在我的老板面前好好炫耀一下.
Like maybe, like maybe somehow you want to show me up in front of my boss.
杰森:可我有这样做的必要吗?
Jason: Why would I want to do that?
麦琪:这是因为你在潜意识里是反对我去工作的.
Maggie: Because on that subconscious level, you resent my working.
杰森:反对你去工作?
Jason: Resent your working?
麦琪:你已经说出来了.
Maggie: There you said it.
杰森:麦琪,我希望你工作,
Jason: Maggie, I love you working.
并且我一直都是这样想的.我希望你能过得充实,
And I always have, I loved you fulfill it,
我也不介意你工作时间有多长,就连你用自己的姓我也不在乎.
I don't mind the long hours as I didn't mind you using your maid name.
麦琪:这跟我的姓有什么关系?
Maggie: What my maid name got to do with this?
杰森:哦,没有,没有,抱歉!那就不提了.
Jason: Oh, nothing, nothing.I am sorry, don't mention it.
麦琪:但这让你心烦了.
Maggie: It bothers you.
杰森:不,不,是的,是的.
Jason: No, no.yes yes.
麦琪:我本想你会理解我的.
Maggie: I thought you understood.
杰森:以前我都可以理解,但现在在超级市场也有人叫我马龙先生,
Jason: Yes I understood until people started coming up to me at supermarket
就连那警卫也来查我的身份.
called me Mr.Marlon, until the guard started patting my bottom.
麦琪:杰森,那是他的工作需要.
Maggie: Jason, he is just doing his job.
杰森:要是你还是麦琪·西沃,
Jason: Maggie, he wouldn't be doing anything if you are still Maggie Seaver.
他就不会对我这样了.以前我喜欢读你为小报撰写的文章,
How I used to love when I saw the bylines I was so proud of by
特别是看到麦琪·西沃的署名我心里是多么的自豪啊.
Maggie Seaver that's when you worked for a little paper.
麦琪:小报?
Maggie: Little?
杰森:哦,不,不,你知道我意思的.
Jason: Oh, no.you know what I mean.
麦琪:你不想让我去做大事,
Maggie: You just don't want me to have a big job.
是不是我只配做一些不起眼的小事?
Just a cute teeny-weeny little... career.
杰森:麦琪,你工作过度而导致太累了,
Jason: You know you overworked, Maggie, you are tired.
所有的时间都用在谈你的工作上了,每天一早起来你就开始呕吐.
We always talk about your work.Then get up in the morning.You start barfing.
麦琪:抱歉!
Maggie: I am so sorry.
杰森:难道你还不明白?麦琪!
Jason: You know what?I tell something else, I've noticed recently, Maggie?
麦琪:看来我们是不能再共同生活下去了.
Maggie: Lately we've been drifting apart.
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yeah.
麦琪:杰森,你老实说吧,究竟是我疯了?还是你内心根本就愿意我去工作.
Maggie: Jason, level with me, am I crazy?In your deep down inside of you
is that part of your wishes that I didn't work
杰森:得了.
Jason: No, come on.
麦琪:老实讲吧!
Maggie: Be honest.
杰森:真的说实话?
Jason: Honest?
麦琪:想说什么就说什么!
Maggie: Totally honest and selfish.
杰森:好的,你没有发疯!
Jason: Ok, you are not crazy.
麦琪:我能体会得到.
Maggie: I sensed it.
杰森:麦琪,
Jason: Maggie, that is just a little part of me,
那仅仅是我的部分想法,我只是想知道事业对你到底有多重要,
the rest of me just knows how important the career is.
是你让我说实话的.
You want me to be honest.
麦琪:曾经我想过也不再工作了,
Maggie: You know that's a part of me that I wished I didn't work either.
可是杰森,
But then there is another part of me, Jason,
成为一名记者是我一直的梦想.
that dreamed of a career in journalism further long as I can remember.
杰森:现在你老实回答我.
Jason: All right, now let me ask you to be totally honest.
你后悔过吗?
Don't you ever resent,
就是那种后悔为辞去工作而后又得要重新开始的念头,
just sometimes you resent for a moment if you had to quit your career
也许有时这种念头只是很短暂的!
and start all over again.
麦琪:不,杰森,这和我去工作没有任何关系!
Maggie: No, Jason, there is no, just no connection.
杰森:得了,一定要老实讲,想到什么说什么!
Jason: Come on, Just, just, just be honest.Remember to be totally selfish.
麦琪:杰森,
Maggie: Jason, I have never ever regretted quitting news week and having
我并没有因为三个孩子的缘故离开而后悔
the three children.
杰森:哦,麦琪,这我知道的.但是你有没有想过当时要是没有辞去的工作,你现在又会怎么样呢?
Jason: Oh, I know that, Maggie.But don't you ever ask yourself that ...I couldn't be around now by ever quitting Newsweek.
麦琪:偶尔吧!
Maggie: Occasionally.
杰森:什么时候?
Jason: Hum, When?
麦琪:就是当我追赶那些比我年龄小一半的年轻人和当我担心自己的事业再也不能成功的时候,而现在我也明白你担心的也就是这个.
Maggie: Whenever I am running to keep up with the kids half my age.
Whenever I am frightened that I might never really succeed.
And now I see that you are afraid that I just might.
杰森:喂!是的,麦琪·马龙在家.
Jason: Hello.Yes, Maggie Marlon is here.
麦琪:喂!你好,博嗨医生.不,现在不行.什么?不,你能肯定吗?谢谢.
Maggie: Hello.Hi, Doctor Bhl.No, this isn't good time, right.What?No.are you
sure?Thank you
杰森:麦琪,我们想出解决办法的,我只是不知道……
Jason: Maggie, I know we can work this thing out.I don't know how ...
麦琪:我们要多一个孩子了!
Maggie: We are going to have a baby.
杰森:当然,这种方法也行.
Jason: Sure, that's one way we......
麦琪:博嗨医生为我作了怀孕检查,那是我的体检的一部分.
Maggie: That's part of my physical.Doctor Buhl ran a pregnancy test.
杰森:原来你不是觉得我恶心,而是你肚子里的孩子,这太棒了!
Jason: You were barfing not at me, but barfing at having a baby.So great!
麦琪:也许这就是为什么看到你和我老板关系密切时,
Maggie: Maybe that's why I was so intensified when you hit it off with
我这么紧张了.
my boss.
杰森:我想也许是我太嫉妒你的工作.
Jason: I know probably it was too jealous, I probably show you up at work.
麦琪:那就对了!
Maggie: That's so sweet.
杰森:现在我是不是高兴的像个傻瓜?
Jason: Am I a jerk?
麦琪:真高心你承认你像个大傻瓜了.
Maggie: But it's the so sweet of you to admit you are a total jerk.
杰森:我没有说是大傻瓜!
Jason: I didn't say a total jerk?
麦琪:哦,是我加的
Maggie: Oh, yeah.I add that.
杰森:我们家要有个新生命了.
Jason: A brand new, little baby.
麦琪:刚刚我们还说不能共同生活下去了.
Maggie: And we thought we were drifting apart.
杰森:肯定也离不了多远.
Jason: Well, obviously not that apart.
麦琪:刚刚我们俩都在争什么啊?
Maggie: What was it we were just talking about?
杰森:我不记得了!
Jason: I don't remember.
麦琪:都是我们俩的事.我们俩都有各自不同的小愿望.
Maggie: It was about the fact, wasn't it?There is a tiny part that we... we should think we are different.
杰森:是的,不过我们的主题还是一致的.
Jason: Yeah, but there is a mother big part that just links just well.
麦琪:快去告诉孩子们吧!
Maggie: Let's go tell the kids.
杰森:嗨,等等,等明早再说吧.今晚就先自私一点,
Jason: Look, wait, wait, wait, in the morning. Let's just be selfish.
我们俩知道就行了.孩子!怎么会有的呢?
Keep this for ourselves.Have a baby?Haha...
麦琪:那是真的!
Maggie: Yes.
杰森:怎么回事哪?
麦琪:让我告诉你吧!
00:23:06,900
Jason: How did this happen? Maggie: Let me show you.